Maniac
Just a steel town girl on a
Saturday night lookin' for the fight of her life
In the real-time world no one sees her at all they all say she's crazy
Locking rhythms to the beat of her heart changing movement into life
She has danced into the danger zone
When a dancer becomes a dance
It can cut you like a knife if the gift becomes the fire
On a wire between will and what will be
She's a maniac maniac on the floor
And she's dancing like she's never danced before
On the ice brittle line of insanity is a place most never see
It's a hard won place of mystery
Touch it but can't hold it
You worked all your life for that moment in time it could come or pass you by
It's a push shove world but there's always a chance if the hunger stays the night
There's a cold kinetic heat
Struggling stretching for the peak
Never stopping with her head against the wind
She's a maniac maniac at your door
And she's dancing like she's never danced before
Ooh oh
Oh
It can cut you like a knife if the gift becomes the fire
On a wire between will and what will be
She's a maniac maniac at your love
And she's dancing like she's never danced before
Maniac maniac at your love